New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pesticide and Pest Information, 1977-2000; 7; 12.44 cubic ft.
  - Subseries 2: Pesticides, Undated; 7.2
    - Pyrethrins and Pyrethrolds, General Information, 1985-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 8)
    - Pyrethrins, Pyrethrum, 1976-2002 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 9)
    - Pyridine, 1993-1996 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 10)
    - Pyriproxyfen, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 11)
    - Pyriminil, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 12)
    - Pymetrozine, 2001-2002 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 13)
    - Quwenling, Article, 2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 14)
    - Quinalphos, Article, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 15)
    - Quinclorac, General Information, 2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 16)
    - Quizalofop Ethyl, General Information, 1988 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 17)
    - Resmethrin, General Information, 1988-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 18)
    - Resmethrin a.k.a. Scourge, Information Packet, 1987-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 19)
    - Road Salt, General Information, 1996-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 20)
    - Rotenone, Information Packet, 1996 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 21)
    - Rotenone, General Information, 1979-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 22)
    - Rozol Chlorophacinone, Chemical Information, 1984 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 23)
    - Ryania, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 24)
    - Sabadilla, General Information, 1987 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 25)
    - Safrole, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 26)
    - Select, General Information, 1992 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 27)
    - Selenium, General Information, 1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 28)
    - Silica Gel, General and Product Information, 1988-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 29)
    - Simazine, General Information, 1984-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 30)
    - Simazine, Information Packet, 1984-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 31)
    - Sodium arsenate, General Information, 1986-1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 32)
    - Sodium arsenate, General Information, 1988-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 33)
    - Sodium Benzoate, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 34)
    - Sodium Chlorate, General Information, 1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 35)
    - Sodium Cyanide, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 36)
    - Sodium Fluoride, General Information, 1984-1987 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 37)
    - Sodium Fluoroacetate, General Information, 1982-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 38)
    - Sodium Hexafluorosilicate, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 39)
    - Sodium and Calcium Hypochlorite, 1986; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 40)
    - Sodium Omadine, General Information, 1985 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 41)
    - Sodium Propionate, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 42)
    - Sodium Salt of Fomesafen, General Information, 1987 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 43)
    - Sonar (Aquatic Herbicide)/New York State Environmental Enforcement, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 44)
    - Sonar/Fluridone, NYCAP Official Statement, and NYS Memos, and Correspondence, 1986-1996 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 45)
    - Spinosad, Chemical and Product Information, 1997-2002 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 46)
    - Starlicide, General Information, 1985 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 47)
    - Stoddard Solvent, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 48)
    - Streptomycin, General Information, 1988 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 49)
    - Strychnine Alkaloid and Sulfate, General Information, 1988 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 50)
    - Sugar Ester, "Nontoxic", Article, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 51)
    - Sulfluramid, Information Packet, Draft, 1994-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 52)
    - Sulfonylureas, General Information, 1991-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 53)
    - Sulfonylureas a.k.a. Oust, Glean, Information Packet, 1985-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 54)
    - Sulfometuron Methyl (Oust), General Information, 1985-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 55)
    - Sulfotepp, General Information, 1988 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 56)
    - Sulfur, General Information, 1986-1994 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 57)
    - Sulfuryl Flouride, Information Packet, 1985-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 58)
    - TDE, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 59)
    - Tebufenozide, General Information, 1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 60)
    - Tebuthiuron, General Information, 1987-1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 61)
    - Tefluthrin, General Information, 1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 62)
    - Temephos, General Information, 1996-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 63)
    - Terbacil, General Information, 1987-1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 64)
    - Terbufos, General Information, 1987-1992 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 65)
    - Terbutryn, General Information, 1986 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 66)
    - Terpene polychlorinates, Strobane, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 67)
    - Terephthalic Acid, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 68)
    - 1, 1, 2, 2, -Tetrachloroethane, General Information, 1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 69)
    - Tertachloroethylene, General Information, 1989-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 70)
    - Tetrachlovinphos, General Information, 1988 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 71)
    - Tetramethrin, Information Packet, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 72)
    - Tetramethrin, General Information, 1987-1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 73)
    - Thallium Sulfate, General Information, 1995; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 74)
    - Thiabendazole, General Information, 2001; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 75)
    - Thiobencarb, Bolero, General Information, 1985 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 76)
    - Thiodicarb, General Information, 1984-1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 77)
    - Thionazin, Zinophos, General Information, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 78)
    - Thiophanate Ethyl, General Information, 1986 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 79)
    - Thiophanate-methyl, Information Packet, 1986-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 80)
    - Thiram, Information Packet, 1984-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 81)
    - Thymol, General Information, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 82)
    - Toluene, 1986-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 83)
    - Toxaphene, General Information, 1990-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 84)
    - TPTH (Triphenyltin hydroxide) General Information, 1984 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 85)
    - Tralomethrin, 2001; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 86)
    - Triademefon, 2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 87)
    - Triadimenol, Baytan, 1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 88)
    - Triallate, 1987 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 89)
    - Triasulfuron, 1994 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 90)
    - Tribenuron Methyl, 1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 91)
    - Tributyltin (TBT), 1986-2002 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 92)
    - Trichlorfon, 1987-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 93)
    - Trichloroacetic Acid, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 94)
    - Trichloroethylene (TCE), 1990-1997 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 95)
    - Trichlorophenols (TCPs), 1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 96)
    - Triclopyr, Garlon, 1987-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 97)
    - Triclopyr, Information Packet, 1983-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 98)
    - Triclosan, 2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 99)
    - Triclosan, Information Packet, 1998-1999 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 100)
    - Trichoderma Harzianum and Trichoderma Polysporum, 1989 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 101)
    - Triflumizole, Terraguard, 1991; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 102)
    - Trifluoroacetic Acid, 2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 103)
    - Trifluralin, 1985-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 104)
    - Triforine, 1987-2000 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 105)
    - Trimethacarb, 1985 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 106)
    - Triphenyltin, 1989-2002 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 107)
    - Uniconazole-P, 1991 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 108)
    - Vinclozolin, 1994-2001 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 109)
    - Vinyl Chloride, 1997; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 110)
    - Vitamin D3, 1984 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 111)
    - Warfarin, 1985-1998; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 112)
    - Xylene, 1984-2000; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 113)
    - Zinc Borate, 1991; 1995 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 114)
    - Zinc Phosphide, 1985-1991; Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 115)
    - Zinc Sulfate, 1998 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 116)
    - Zinc Sulfide, Undated (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 117)
    - Zineb, 1986-1990 (Box 7(Propo-Z) (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 118)
    - 2, 4-D (dichlorophenoxyacetic acid), Environmental Protection Agency Review, Carcinogenicity Testing, 1977-1993 (Box 8 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 1)
    - Fluridone, Sonar, Lake George Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 8 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 2)
    - Mosquitoes, Adirondack Communities Against Aerial Pesticides, News Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 3)